They say
A woman's heart is a needle in the sea.
Wrong, my darlings.
A man's desire is the needle.
And what you need to do
is make him prick his hand to come to you.
Remember, playing hard to get is not rejection.
Giving in
is just to provoke his aggressiveness.
When he goes crazy for you
and crosses the line,
congratulations,
he will be your prisoner.
From tomorrow on,
order me a bunch of flowers every day
and send them to the Lin Group
for Guan Tiantian.
The case of Niudingshan's divorce
seems to be an emotional dispute,
but in fact,
the suspect Bai Qiang
using legal loopholes
and human weaknesses
to carry out systematic plunder.
The existing evidence points to S club.
But
more evidence
may still require further investigation.
Have you been to this place?
Not yet.
This S club is very strictly managed.
It's hard to get in without connections.
But according to my observation these days,
those who come in and out
are all socialites.
I think it is very likely that this is
Bai Qiang's base
for allegedly defrauding marriage from Niu Dingshan.
Times are changing,
and so are the methods of crime.
When crime
wears the gloves of socialite education,
the judicial system
must sharpen its lens
to see through the facade.
If we tolerate this kind of criminal pattern,
there will be more victims
like Niudingshan
falling prey to the hunt.
Jiang,
we need
more evidence now.
You need to work harder.
Okay, sir.
Vivian.
Don't worry.
Bai Qiang's case
is just a regular divorce case.
I remember
you just ended a marriage not long ago.
What happened this time?
Oh.
Ms. Tian,
we all have to move on.
I'll need your help
with this one.
Thank you.
It's urgent.
The previous lawyer
was unreliable.
I wouldn't have come to you otherwise.
You're welcome, Ms. Wei.
I'll leave you to it.
Bye.
Tell me,
what do you want?
Ms. Tian,
this time, the Niu Mountains
is a real fat sheep.
Bai Qiang,
what exactly do you want to do?
You just escaped
from a life-threatening marriage.
That's why
I don't want to go back to the hard life.
Zhao Zhiwei, that bastard, made me understand
that all feelings
are fake.
Only money and ability are real.
Ms. Wei said
as long as I do as S club taught me,
I can get this amount of money
from Niudingshan.
You're playing with fire.
This is no longer a simple divorce case.
You're doing this on purpose.
So what?
That's how men treat us, isn't it?
Come on, Tian.
Just help me out.
Like last time.
Once this is done,
I'll give you 30%.
Oh, no,
40%.
Much better deal than your lawyer fees.
What do you take me for?
And what do you take yourself for?
Stop pretending to be noble.
Just wait and see.
I'll live better than all of you.
It's password protected.
Try his birthday.
Mr. Guan,
what are you doing here?
Assistant Chen,
I'm here to deliver documents to Mr. Lin.
He's in a meeting.
I see.
Assistant Chen,
could you please tell him
that I need all the overseas project documents
and contracts from the past five years
of the group?
No problem.
Mr. Lin has already given instructions.
As long as it's needed by Guan Law Firm,
it will be provided.
Thank you.
Zhan Shan,
what do you think
of the new legal counsel
by Jiming's side?
She's from Guan Law Firm.
is quite capable.
She has helped Mr. Lin solve many problems.
Problems?
I think she's a master at creating problems.
I heard that Jiming
trusts her
particularly.
That's right.
They
also made an appointment to go to the beach
this afternoon.
I heard that
the cases she has been working on recently
are all
aiming at the Lin Group.
Tang Group,
Huamiao,
Zhao Zhiwei,
if there are too many coincidences,
it's not a coincidence.
Keep an eye on her.
Yes.
Sorry
for the wait.
You look
different today.
I told you
to call me Jiming.
You're
pretty professional.
I've played a few times before.
Just a beginner.
The horse I chose for you today, Chasing Wind,
is very gentle.
Looks like
you have something you're not good at too.
Yeah,
I'm not very familiar with this.
Relax a bit.
Don't hold the reins too tightly.
Follow its rhythm.
Don't keep staring at the horse's head.
Look further ahead.
Thank you.
For what?
For helping me relax.
Although
I'm not very good at it,
trying new things occasionally
is quite nice.
What about you?
When can you
let go of your usual
and relax a bit?
I'm already relaxed.
How about
I show you around?
Sure,
be careful.
You're not good at this.
Why did you agree to ride a horse?
Because you wanted to come.
I just want to
to know more about you
outside of work.
Relax.
If you're so tense,
the horse will get nervous too.
Ah!